ethnicelebs.com 2019-11-27

# Privacy Policy – Ethnicity of Celebs | What Nationality Ancestry Race

**ETHNICELEBS.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

**1.   Introduction**

Welcome to Ethnicelebs.com.  Please read our Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy carefully, as you are agreeing to be bound by both legal documents as a condition of being given permission to use our Service.

**2.   Definitions**

Throughout this document, we may use certain words or phrases, and it is important that you understand the meaning of them.  The following is a non-exhaustive list of definitions of words and phrases found in this document:

“Ethnicelebs” refers to our business, which is a sole proprietorship operating as “EthniCelebs.com”; our Site: our Service; or a combination of all or some of the preceding definitions, depending on the context of the word;

“Service” refers to the services that we provide through our Site, including our the provision of information about celebrities, and the opportunity for Users to submit information about celebrities;

“Site” refers to our website, [www.ethnicelebs.com](http://www.ethnicelebs.com/);

“User” refers to registered and unregistered users of Ethnicelebs and, without limiting the generality of the foregoing, includes general visitors to Ethnicelebs’ Site who do not otherwise interact with the Site;

“You” refers to you, the person who is governed by this Privacy Policy.

**3.   Information Collected**

Identifying Information

We may collect certain personal information from you if you volunteer it in your submissions, though we request that you do not do so for your own privacy.  The information we collect from you, to the extent that it is private, is disclosed only in accordance with our Terms of Service and/or this Privacy Policy.

Non-Identifying Information

Whenever you visit our Site, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your IP address, referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, and Internet Service Provider.  Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

**4.   Use of Your Information**

We may use your information to:

  * Enhance or improve User experience, our Site, or our Service.
  * Perform any other function that we believe in good faith is necessary to protect the security or proper functioning of our Site or Service.

#### Processing Personal Data

“Personal Data” is any information that may directly or indirectly identify you.

“Processing” of this information refers to collection, recording, organisation, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.

A “Data Controller” is a person who is responsible for processing personal data and determining the purpose and methods of processing it. For CelebHeights.com, the data controller is Rob Paul.

By visiting and using this site, you consent to the Processing of your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Personal Information We Collect and Usage

**Access Logs:**  
The Web Server stores logs of each request, in the form of an IP address, URL/file, User Agent and timestamp. This is necessary for diagnostic, management and site improvement purposes. These logs are purged from the server on a Daily basis.

**Unauthorised Access Logs:**  
The Web Server stores logs of any attempts to access restricted services. This includes IP address, a timestamp and type of attempted intrusion. Under the Computer Misuse act, these type of attempts are illegal, and as such, logs may be used as evidence in a court of law.

**Visitor Comments and Votes**  
The Web server stores data supplied by visitors who submit public comments.

This information is used to identify commenters and prevent abuse of the website, by storing a Username, Email and IP address in our database. Comments are stored with a submission date, username and IP address.

Email addresses are never published. We only display the Comment, date of submission and the Username.

If you contact us by email, a record of our correspondence will be kept.

#### Information Sharing

We may disclose your personal data when necessary in order to comply with a legal requirement, or to protect your vital interest or the vital interests of others.

We use 3rd Party services for Website analytics and Website advertising:

A cookie is a small textual file, stored by the visitor’s browser on behalf of a website to let us recognise and remember you. It has an expiry date.

**Google Analytics (GA)**  
We use GA to track interaction, like number of visits, pages viewed, to help understand how the site engages with visitors, and to help maintain and improve the experience. GA is also used in order to show visitors an accurate portrayal of the most popular celebrities on the site.  
Although GA records data such as an approximate geographical location, device, browser and operating system, none of this information personally identifies you to us. We set a flag – “[anonymizeIp](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052?hl=en&ref_topic=2919631)” – which requests GA to anonymize all IP addresses. [More Information](https://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html). To opt-out of Google Analytics tracking, visit: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> to get an add-on, that opts you out.

We also use Google Custom Search to help visitors find content on the site. It uses cookies to display ads.

**Google Adsense**  
Google uses cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to celebheights.com or other websites. Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and [its partners](https://policies.google.com/privacy/partners) to serve relevant adverts to you, based on visits to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.  
**Within the European Economic Area:**  We display Non-Personalised ads which may be based on the topic of a page or a general geographical area. Adsense non-personalised cookies are needed for frequency capping, aggregated reporting (statistics) and to help combat fraud and abuse of the Adsense Network.  
Google lets you manage preferences and whether to receive google ads on the web or not – <https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>

**5.   Accessing, Editing, and Removing Your Information**

Users may in some cases be able to review and edit the personal information they have provided to us by logging into your account on the Site and editing their account.  Although most changes may occur immediately, information may still be stored in a web browser’s cache.  We take no responsibility for stored information in your cache, or in other devices that may store information, and disclaim all liability of such.  In addition, we may, from time to time, retain residual information about you in our backup and/or database.

You may request a copy of your data stored in the WordPress database (comments etc.) by contacting the [website admin](https://ethnicelebs.com/contact-admin).

**6.   Cookies**

We use cookies to remember your preferences and track advertisements.  For these reasons, it is necessary that you enable cookies in your browser, and you hereby acknowledge that we have informed you of our use of cookies and that you consent to our use of cookies in relation to your computer system.

We also use Google AdSense on our Site, which uses the DoubleClick cookie.  For information on how to disable the DoubleClick cookie, please visit [http://www.google.ca/policies/technologies/ads/](https://www.google.ca/policies/technologies/ads/).

**7.   Third Party Websites**

Ethnicelebs may post links to third party websites on its Site.  These third party websites are not screened for privacy or security issues by Ethnicelebs, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third party websites.

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to members of the Service or Site.  Ethnicelebs bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website.  Please review the privacy policy and terms of service for each site you visit through third party links.

**8.   Third Party Access to Your Information**

Although you are entering into an Agreement with Ethnicelebs to disclose your information to us, we do use third party individuals and organizations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts, and others.

Throughout the course of our provision of our Service to you, we may delegate our authority to collect, access, use, and disseminate your information.  For example, our web host stores the information that you provide us, and we may hire outside contractors to perform maintenance or assist us in securing our website.

It is therefore necessary that you grant the third parties we may use in the course of our business the same rights that you afford us under this Privacy Policy.  For this reason, you hereby agree that for every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems.  You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.

**9.   Release of Your Information for Legal Purposes**

At times it may become necessary, for legal purposes, to release your information in response to a request from a government agency or a private litigant.  You agree that we may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter.  In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either.  We may also proactively report you, and release your information to, third parties where we believe that it is prudent to do so for legal reasons, such as our belief that you have engaged in fraudulent activities.  You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants.

**10.   Security Measures**

We take certain measures to enhance the security of our Site and Service, as it is in our interest to do so.   However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your information.  It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

**11.   International Transfer**

Your information may be transferred to – and maintained on – computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Ethnicelebs transfers Personal Information to the United States and/or Australia and processes it there.  Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

**12.   Amendments**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time.  When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will update this page.  You must read this page each time you use our Service, and your continued use of our Service constitutes your acceptance of any such amendments.

Last Modified:  May 25, 2018
